I keep seeing all of this.
Taylor Lorenz is terrible.
Taylor Lorenz bungled the article.
Taylor Lorenz is a hypocrite.
Did y'all get dark money or nah?
Anything else is irrelevant.
Did you get dark money or nah?
Was you giving out dark money or nah?
Because otherwise you just sound like the rest of these mofos.
It's deflecting and projecting.
Did you give the dark money?
Did you take the dark money?
That's it.
As somebody who has watched conservatives create a narrative that I lost a debate or that I got cooked when it's blatantly obvious that I didn't do neither of those.
I can say that y'all non-conservatives just saying it's been debunked.
The article's been debunked without there being like loud debunkage feels like a very similar tactic of if we all just say the same thing loud enough and as repetitive as enough, then people will just believe it.
So, again, if I've missed the debunkery, put me on.
If I missed the nah, we didn't do it.
Look, tell me.
Because I haven't seen it on the internet.
But I will say, both of y'all sound crazy.
Jams and pubs.
Both of y'all sound a mess.
If we're keeping it honest.